grocerycouponcart.com 2019-06-07

# Free Grocery Coupons, Printable Coupons - Grocery Coupon Cart

Last Updated:  September 24th, 2015

This is the Privacy Policy of GroceryCouponCart.com (“us”, “we”, or “our” ) for your use of all pages and services provided on our website (collectively, the “Site”). 

We respect the privacy of those who access and/or use the Site (“you”, “your”, “user” or collectively “users”) and are committed to protecting the personally identifiable information we collect.

1\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

If this Privacy Policy changes, we will post all changes in an amended version with a new “Last Updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

2. ****INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT****

We collect two types of information from you. The first type is personal information that you actively choose to disclose (“Active Information”) and the second type is anonymous aggregate information collected in a manner not visible to you or others visiting the Site (“Passive Information”).

**a. Active Information** **.** Examples of personally identifiable information that you provide to us may include your first and last name, date of birth, address, and email address. In providing Active Information, you consent and agree to being contacted with information related to your inquiry and/or information regarding our or third parties’ products and services. If you provide personally identifiable information to us, you may later elect to have that information deleted from our files, or kept from being used by us for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the opt-out procedures set forth below.

**b. Passive Information** **.** We record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the information you click on, your browser type, IP address, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We may also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site.

3\. HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED

We may share or sell your Active and/or Passive Information to our marketing partners and affiliates to provide you with commercial products that may be of interest. We also use this information to better target content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience.

**4\. USE OF COOKIES** ****

We use cookies to store users’ preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that users are not repeatedly offered the same material and to customize any newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We may share, sell, or license cookies collected from your browser and hard drive to third-party advertisers. These authorized third parties may link your name, address, and e-mail address to other information which they collect, such as past online/offline purchase information and Web usage from other sites. To learn more about this practice click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. You may disable cookies by adjusting the settings on your Web browser. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so you may wish to review the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Note, however, that you may be required to enable cookies in order to use certain functions on our Site.

Additionally, emails we send may contain a bit of code known as a “web beacon.” This code allows us to understand the time and date of when a user has opened an email and when he/she has utilized a link within the email to visit a website. Our web beacons do not collect personally identifiable information. Users wishing to disable our web beacons should do so by turning images “off” in their email client (e.g., Outlook, Outlook Express). Please see your email client for more information.”

5\. DO-NOT-TRACK POLICY FOR CALIFORNIA USERS

We may collect users’ personally identifiable information while their Web browser’s “do-not-track” features – or other mechanisms that provide choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about consumers’ online activities – are activated. Further, while using our Site, third parties may collect users’ personally identifiable information relating to their online activities while “do-not-track” technologies and similar mechanisms are activated.

6\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

We may share, license, or sell information we collect to third parties for various marketing purposes, including their online marketing programs.  We also reserve the unequivocal right to release all your information, to the maximum extent permitted by law in the event that: (i) we believe that the Site is being or has been used to commit unlawful acts, (ii) the information is subpoenaed or otherwise required in a court proceeding, (iii) you violate or breach an agreement with the Site, (iv) you have submitted fraudulent or otherwise invalid information to this Site, (v) we believe that you may harm, or have harmed, the property or other rights of us, our employees, the Site’s other users or any other third party, (vi) we are sold to or otherwise acquired by any individual, entity or organization (i.e. to a successor entity in the event of sale of the business, including merger, bankruptcy or other ownership change), or (vii) when we otherwise deem it necessary or appropriate. We may disclose any record or communication to any third party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the requirements of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, or any other applicable state or federal law, rule or regulation.

7\. OPTING-OUT

If you no longer wish to receive newsletter or promotional communications from us, you may opt-out by following the instructions included in each newsletter or promotional communication or by contacting us as provided in this Privacy Policy. You may continue to receive email communications from us for up to five (5) business days from the time we receive your unsubscribe request. Please note that we can only control our own mailing list and policies. Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and you may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their communications.

8\. ACCESS/ACCURACY

To the extent that you do provide us with certain personally identifiable information, we strive to maintain the accuracy of this information. Our goal is to provide a means to contact us should you need to review, update or correct your information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible through the Site, you may send your request to review, update or correct your personally identifiable information to Team@grocerycouponcart.com and we will make reasonable efforts to comply as soon as possible.

9\. SECURITY OF INFORMATION

Use of the Site is at your own risk. We do, however, make reasonable efforts to secure your information, including, but not limited to, monitoring our network and data for intrusions. We also use industry-accepted standards to protect your information, including SSL encryption if transmitting sensitive information. Communications you may have with us via email or mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information.

10\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

The Site may contain links to third party Web sites including sites with which we have no affiliation. We are not responsible for their privacy practices. It is recommended you read the privacy policies on all such third party Web sites.

11\. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Beginning January 1, 2005, under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to either: (i) a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided; or (ii) to be notified of a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with third parties. We have elected the second option. To opt-out of having your information shared with third parties going forward, simply email us at [insert email address] with the words “Opt-Out” in the subject header.[  
](file:///C:/Users/Dayne/Desktop/WeHeartFreebies%20com%20Privacy%20Policy%2010-23-13.docx#_msocom_1)

12\. CHILDREN

If you are under 18, you may not access or use the Site.  BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OLD.  In compliance with COPPA, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from users under 13.

13\. CONTACT INFORMATION

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or wish to opt-out as provided above, you may email us at Team@grocerycouponcart.com or send us correspondence at the following address:

GroceryCouponCart.com  
8466 N Lockwood Ridge Rd., Ste 143  
Sarasota, FL 34243
